

# YOUSSEF BEDOUI

FULL STACK JS DEVELOPER

#### Contact



+216 93 576 828



Jozefbedoui@gmail.com



https://www.linkedin.com/in/youssef-bedoui-63661a201/



https://github.com/Youssef-Bedoui?tab=repositories



https://youssefbedoui.site



## **Profil Statement**

Full-Stack web-developer graduated from RBK TUNISIA RebootKamp. Hard-working programmer with a good experience in team-work and communication , Self-learning is one of my strengths builded during many project I worked on that gives me power and energy to develop my skills and potentials in the field .

# **Projects**

### E-Tafakna Mobile Application (Startup)

#### Frontend Developer | Team | 3 Months

- Using React Native I build the user Interface for the app.
- Using React JS to build a user interface for the admin dashboard .
- Using bootstrap and CSS, I styled my application.
- Using Express.js, I build the app API.
- Using MySQL, I create a database to store user informations and contracts .

#### **Technologies:**

- React Native
- Node Js
- Express Js
- Bootstrap
- Cloudinary
- DOX templater
- CSS
- mySQL

#### **Key Achievement:**

I developed a mobile application that will make the user able to sign and generate many types of contracts without need to move to the Administrative Institutions of the state.

# **Technical Skills**

#### Frontend:

JavaScript,React JS, Angular, Vue JS, React native, CSS,Bootstrap, Cloudinary

#### Backend:

Node JS, Express JS, Mongo DB, Mysql

### **Soft Skills**

Attention to detail

Adaptability

Flexibility

Time-management

Leadership

# Language

English: Acceptable
French: Pre-intermediate
Arabic: Fluent

# Interest

Gaming

Gardening

**Photography** 

Listening to music

#### **EvenToGo**

#### Full-Stack developer | Solo | One Week

- Using Vue.js I build the user Interface for the app. and Dashboard for admin.
- Using Bootstrap and CSS, I styled my application.
- Using Express.js, I build the app Api.
- Using Mysql, I create a database for the app.

#### **Technologies:**

- Vue Js
- Express Js
- CSS
- BOOTSTRAP
- mySQL

#### **Key Achievement:**

I developed a website that help peoples to check the nearest events that they can attend.

#### Menyoo

#### Frontend Developer | Solo | One Week

- Using React.js I build the user Interface for the website.
- Using Bootstrap and CSS, I styled my application.
- Using Express.js, I build the app Api.
- Using Mysql, I create a database for the app.

#### **Technologies:**

- React Js
- Express Js
- CSS
- mySQL

#### **Key Achievement:**

I developed a website that will help the restaurant owner to generate a personalized menu for their costumers .

### Klupea

Full-stack Developer | Solo training | 4 months

- Using React.js I build the user Interface for the website.
- Using Bootstrap and CSS and materialUI, I styled my application.
- Using Express.js, I build the app Api.
- Using Mysql, I create a database for the app.
- using Redux state management system to manage app data.

# **Education**

Higher Institute Of Language - Nabel 2017-2020

Bachelors in Arabic Language

# Certification

RebootCamp TUNISIA - Ariana Dec 2021, Juin 2022

Full-Stack JS Developer

# **Courses and Training**

IBH Training Center - Kelibia Feb 2020 - Apr 2020

Certification in Web Development

Gained extensive training in Html, CSS, mySQL

Designet Training Center - Menzel Temim

Feb 2022 - March 2022

Certification in React JS / Angular JS

Gained basic training in React and Angular.

Sololearn

May 2023

Certification in React JS + Redux

Gained a training in react and redux .

# **Experience:**

E-tafakna Mobile App | Statrtup June 2022 - Sep 2022

**Position: Full-stack Developer** 

Tasks: Work on frontend design and backend build and implementation.

**DESIGNET Web Agency | Menzel** 

**Temime** 

July2023 - Sep2023

**Position: Frontend Developer** 

Tasks: Work on frontend design of

websites.

#### **Technologies:**

- React Is
- Express Js
- CSS
- mySQL
- Stripe payment
- Redux(update)

#### **Key Achievement:**

I developed an example for a simple and easy E-commerce app where you can buy Clothes .

### **MovieLights**

#### Front-end Developer | Solo training | 1 month

- Using React.js and react-redux I build the user Interface for the website.
- Using CSS and materialUI, I styled my application.
- I worked with The Movie Database API to get the application data .

#### **Technologies:**

- React Js + Redux
- CSS
- The Movie Database API

#### **Key Achievement:**

I developed a web application to help users get an overview of movies and select the best ones to watch.

#### **Rainy Forecast**

Front-end Developer | Solo training | 2 weeks

- Using React.js | build the user Interface for the website.
- Using CSS and materialUI, I styled my application.
- I worked with The Weatherapi API to get the application data.

#### **Technologies:**

- React Js
- CSS
- Weatherapi Database API

#### **Key Achievement:**

I developed a web application to help users check forecast for 3 days of any place around the world . .